<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!--
    Each entry is in four parts: name, dates, quotation, bio 
    
    NOTE: If a new entry is inserted before "Al Capone", adjust the baseIndexImage in the main activity!
    -->
    <array name="quotations">
        <item>Abraham Lincoln      #(1809-1865)  #Folks are usually about as happy as they make their minds up to be.#An American president serving from 1861 until his assassination in 1865. Lincoln led the United States through its Civil War. In so doing he preserved the Union, abolished slavery, strengthened the national government and modernized the economy.</item>
        <item>Agatha Christie      #(1890-1976)  #The best time to plan a book is while you\'re doing the dishes.#An crime writer of novels, short stories, and plays. She also wrote six romances under the name Mary Westmacott, but she is best remembered for the 66 detective novels and 14 short story collections she wrote under her own name.</item>
        <item>Al Capone            #(1899-1947)  #Vote early, and vote often.           #An American gangster who led a Prohibition-era crime syndicate. The Chicago Outfit, which subsequently also became known as the “Capones”, was dedicated to smuggling and bootlegging liquor, and other illegal activities, such as prostitution.</item>
        <item>Albert Einstein      #(1879-1955)  #The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits.#A German-born physicist who developed the general theory of relativity.  Best known for his mass–energy equivalence formula E = mc2 (which has been dubbed \"the world\'s most famous equation\".</item>
        <item>Alexander Pope       #(1688-1744)  #Hope springs eternal.#An English poet best known for his satirical verse and for his translation of Homer. He is the third-most frequently quoted writer in The Oxford Dictionary of Quotations, after Shakespeare and Tennyson.</item>
        <item>Allen Newell         #(1927-1992)  #Science is method. Everything else is commentary.#A compuer scientist and cognitive psychology at the RAND Corporation and at Carnegie Mellon University. He was awarded the ACM\'s Turing Award along with Herbert Simon in 1975 for their basic contributions to artificial intelligence and the psychology of human cognition.</item>
        <item>Amelia Earhart       #(1897-1937)  #Never interrupt someone doing what you said couldn\'t be done.#An aviation pioneer and author. The first female aviator to fly solo across the Atlantic Ocean. During an attempt tocircumnavigate the globe in 1937, Earhart disappeared over the central Pacific Ocean.</item>
        <item>Arnold Swartzenegger #(b. 1947)  #Everybody pities the weak - jealousy you have to earn.#An Austrian-American actor (and politician, businessman, investor, and former professional bodybuilder). Schwarzenegger served two terms as the 38th Governor of California from 2003 until 2011.</item>
        <item>Ayn Rand             #(1905-1982)  #You can avoid reality, but you cannot avoid the consequences of avoiding reality.#An American novelist (and philosopher, playwright, and screenwriter). Known for her two best-selling novels, The Fountainhead and Atlas Shrugged, and for developing a philosophical system she called Objectivism.</item>
        <item>Ben Johnson          #(b. 1961)  #When the gun go off, the race be over.#A Canadian sprinter who won two Olympic bronze medals and an Olympic gold, which were later rescinded. He set consecutive 100 metres world records at the 1987 World Championships in Athletics and the 1988 Summer Olympics, but he was disqualified for doping, losing the Olympic title and both records.</item>
        <item>Benjamin Disraeli    #(1804-1881)  #There are three kinds of lies: lies, damned lies, and statistics.#A British politician (and writer and aristocrat) who twice served as Prime Minister. He played a central role in the creation of the modern Conservative Party. Remembered for his influential voice in world affairs.</item>
        <item>Bertrand Russell     #(1872-1970)  #I would never die for my beliefs because I might be wrong.#A British nobleman (and philosopher, logician, mathematician, historian, and social critic). At various points in his life he considered himself a liberal, a socialist, and a pacifist, but he also admitted that he had never been any of these in any profound sense.</item>
        <item>Bill Clinton         #(b. 1946)  #I didn\'t inhale.                     #An American politician and President of the United States from 1993 to 2001.</item>
        <item>Bill Gates           #(b. 1955)  #640K ought to be enough for anybody.  #An American businessman (and investor, programmer, inventor and philanthropist). Gates is the former chief executive and current chairman of Microsoft, the world\’s largest personal-computer software company, which he co-founded with Paul Allen</item>
        <item>Bill Maher           #(b. 1956)  #If you think you have it tough, read history books.#A stand-up comedian (and television host, political commentator, satirist, author, and actor). Before his current role as the host of HBO\'s Real Time with Bill Maher, Maher hosted a similar late-night talk show called Politically Incorrect.</item>
        <item>Bob Dylan            #(b. 1941)  #All I can be is me, whoever that is.#An American musician (and singer-songwriter, artist, and writer). He has been an influential figure in popular music and culture for more than five decades. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when he was an informal chronicler and a seemingly reluctant figurehead of social unrest.</item>
        <item>Bob Marley           #(1945-1981)  #One good thing about music, when it hits you, you feel no pain.#A Jamaican singer-songwriter who achieved international fame through a series of crossover reggae albums. Starting out in 1963 with the group the Wailers, he forged a distinctive songwriting and vocal style that would later resonate with audiences worldwide.</item>
        <item>Britney Spears       #(b. 1981)  #I get to go to overseas places, like Canada.#A recording artist and entertainer. Born in McComb, Mississippi, and raised in Kentwood, Louisiana, she performed acting roles in stage productions and television shows as a child before signing with Jive Records in 1997. </item>
        <item>Carl Jung            #(1875-1961)  #Show me a sane man and I will cure him for you.#A Swiss psychiatrist and psychotherapist who founded analytical psychology. Jung proposed and developed the concepts of extraversion and introversion; archetypes, and the collective unconscious.</item>
        <item>Carl Sagan           #(1934-1996)  #If you want to make an apple pie from scratch, you must first create the universe.#An American astronomer and author. He published more than 600 scientific papers and articles and was author, co-author or editor of more than 20 books.</item>
        <item>Cass Elliot          #(1941-1974)  #My role in the Mamas and Papas was basically just to sing.#An American singer (also known as Mama Cass) and member of The Mamas &#38; the Papas.</item>
        <item>Charles de Gaulle   #(1890-1970)  #Vive le Québec libre!#A French general and statesman who led the Free French Forces during World War II. He later founded the French Fifth Republic in 1958 and served as its first president from 1959 to 1969.</item>
        <item>Charlton Heston     #(1923-2008)  #Political correctness is tyranny with manners.#An American actor and political activist. As a Hollywood star he appeared in 100 films over the course of 60 years. He is best known for his roles in The Ten Commandments (1956), Ben-Hur (for which he won the Academy Award for Best Actor, 1959), and Planet of the Apes (1968).</item>
        <item>Chaucer              #(1343-1400)  #Time and tide wait for no man.        #An English author known as the Father of English literature.  Widely considered the greatest English poet of the Middle Ages. The first poet to have been buried in the Poet\'s Corner of Westminster Abbey.</item>
        <item>Confucius            #(551-479 BC) #Before you embark on a journey of revenge, dig two graves.#A Chinese teacher (and editor, politician, and philosopher of the Spring and Autumn period of Chinese history). The philosophy of Confucius emphasized personal and governmental morality, correctness of social relationships, justice and sincerity.</item>
        <item>Desmond Tutu         #(b. 1931)  #I\'m not an optimist, I\'m a prisoner of hope.#A South African social rights activist and retired Anglican bishop who rose to worldwide fame during the 1980s as an opponent of apartheid. He was the first black Archbishop of Cape Town and bishop of the Church of the Province of Southern Africa (now the Anglican Church of Southern Africa).</item>
        <item>Dirty Harry          #           #Go ahead, make my day.                #Clint Eastwood\'s role in the 1971 American crime thriller of the same name.  In the role, Eastwood portrays a San Francisco Police Department Inspector named \"Dirty\" Harry Callahan.</item>
        <item>Don Quixote          #           #Facts are the enemy of truth.         #A fictional character in the novel \"The Ingenious Gentleman Don Quixote of La Mancha\" (Spanish: El ingenioso hidalgo don Quijote de la Mancha), by Miguel de Cervantes Saavedra (1547-1616). It follows the adventures of Alonso Quijano, an hidalgo who reads so many chivalric novels that he decides to set out to revive chivalry.</item>
        <item>Dorothy Parker       #(1893-1967)  #Brevity is the soul of lingerie.#An American poet (and short story writer, critic and satirist) best known for her wit, wisecracks, and eye for 20th-century urban foibles.</item>
        <item>Eleanor Roosevelt    #(1884-1962)  #No one can make you feel inferior without your consent.#The First Lady of the United States, holding the post from 1933 to 1945 during her husband President Franklin D. Roosevelt\'s four terms in office. President Harry S. Truman later called her the \"First Lady of the World\" in tribute to her human rights achievements.</item>
        <item>Elvis Presley        #(1935-1977)  #I don\'t know anything about music.  In my line, you don\'t have to.#An American singer (and musician and actor). One of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as \"the King of Rock and Roll\", or simply, \"the King\".</item>
        <item>Emily Dickenson      #(1830-1886)  #A wounded deer leaps the highest.#An American poet born in Amherst, Massachusetts.  From a successful family with strong community ties, she lived a mostly introverted and reclusive life.</item>
        <item>Foster Hewitt        #(1902-1985)  #He shoots, he scores.                 #A Canadian broadcaster most famous for his play-by-play calls for Hockey Night in Canada. He was the son of W. A. Hewitt, and the father of Bill Hewitt.</item>
        <item>Fran Lebowitz        #(b. 1950)  #In real life, I assure you, there is no such thing as algebra.#An American author and public speaker. Lebowitz is known for her sardonic social commentary on American life as filtered through her New York City sensibilities.</item>
        <item>Frank Lloyd Wright   #(1867-1959)  #You can use an eraser on the drafting table or a sledge hammer on the construction site.#An American architect (and interior designer, writer and educator) who designed more than 1000 structures and completed 532 works. Wright believed in designing structures which were in harmony with humanity and its environment, a philosophy he called organic architecture.</item>
        <item>Frank Zappa          #(1940-1993)  #There is more stupidity than hydrogen in the universe, and it has a longer shelf life.#A American musician whose career spanned more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, jazz, orchestral and musique concrète works. He released more than 60 albums with the band The Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist.</item>
        <item>Fred Flintstone      #           #Yubba dubba do.                       #The burly protagonist of the animated sitcom The Flintstones, which aired during prime-time on ABC durinG from 1960 to 1966. Fred is the husband of Wilma Flintstone and father of Pebbles Flintstone. His best friends are his next door neighbors, Barney and Betty Rubble, who have an adopted son named Bamm-Bamm.</item>
        <item>Friedrich Nietzsche  #(1844-1900)  #In heaven all the interesting people are missing.#A German philosopher (and philologist, cultural critic, poet and composer). He wrote several critical texts on religion, morality, contemporary culture, philosophy and science, displaying a fondness for metaphor, irony and aphorism.</item>
        <item>Friendly Giant       #           #Look up, look way up.                 #The lead character in a popular Canadian children\'s television program that aired on CBC Television from September 1958 through to March 1985. It featured three main characters: a giant named Friendly (played by Bob Homme), who lived in a huge castle, along with his puppet animal friends Rusty (a rooster) and Jerome (a giraffe).</item>
        <item>Galileo Galilei      #(1564-1642)  #I do not feel obliged to believe that the same God who has endowed us with sense, reason, and intellect has intended us to forgo their use.#An Italian physicist, mathematician, astronomer, and philosopher who played a major role in the scientific revolution. His achievements include improvements to the telescope and consequent astronomical observations and support for Copernicanism. </item>
        <item>George Bernard Shaw  #(1856-1950)  #The power of accurate observation is frequently called cynicism by those who don\'t have it.#An Irish author who moved to London where he wrote regularly but struggled financially. His play Pygmalion was later made into a film.  The screenplay he wrote for the first version of it won him an Oscar. He wrote more than 60 plays and won many other awards, including the Nobel Prize.</item>
        <item>George Burns         #(1896-1996)  #Happiness is having a large, loving, caring, close-knit family in another city.#An American comedian (and actor and writer). He was one of the few entertainers whose career successfully spanned vaudeville, film, radio, and television. His arched eyebrow and cigar smoke punctuation became familiar trademarks for over three-quarters of a century.</item>
        <item>George Carlin        #(1937-2008)#I\'ve never seen a homeless guy with a bottle of Gatorade.#An American comedian (and writer, social critic, and actor) who won five Grammy Awards for his comedy albums. Noted for his black humor and his thoughts on politics, the English language, psychology, religion, and various taboo subjects.</item>
        <item>George W. Bush        #(b. 1946)  #It\'s clearly a budget.  It\'s got a lot of numbers in it.#An American politician and businessman who served as the 43rd President of the United States from 2001 to 2009 and the 46th Governor of Texas from 1995 to 2000.</item>
        <item>Golda Meir           #(1898-1978)  #Don\'t be so humble.  You are not that great.#An Israeli teacher and politician who became the fourth Prime Minister of Israel. She was described as the \"Iron Lady\" of Israeli politics years before the epithet became associated with Britian\'s Margaret Thatcher.</item>
        <item>Gore Vidal           #(1925-2012)  #A narcissist is someone better looking than you are.#An American writer known for his essays, novels, and plays. As a well-known public intellectual, he was known for his patrician manner and witty aphorisms.</item>
        <item>Groucho Marx         #(1809-1977)  #I never forget a face, but in your case I\'ll be glad to make an exception.#An American comedian and film and television star. He is known as a master of quick wit and widely considered one of the best comedians of the modern era. His rapid-fire, often impromptu delivery of innuendo-laden patter earned him many admirers and imitators.</item>
        <item>H. G. Wells          #(1866-1946)  #Human history becomes more and more a race between education and catastrophe.#An English writer now best known for his work in the science fiction genre. He was also a prolific writer in many other genres, including contemporary novels, history, politics and social commentary, even writing textbooks and rules for war games.</item>
        <item>Henry Kissinger      #(b. 1923)  #The nice thing about being a celebrity is that if you bore people they think it\'s their fault.#An American diplomat and political scientist. A recipient of the Nobel Peace Prize, he served as National Security Advisor and later concurrently as Secretary of State in the administrations of Presidents Richard Nixon and Gerald Ford.</item>
        <item>Hiram Johnson        #(1866-1945)  #The first casualy of war is truth.#An American politician (and isolationist) from California.  He served as the 23rd governor from 1911 to 1917, and as a United States Senator from 1917 to 1945. He was Theodore Roosevelt\'s running mate in the 1912 presidential election on the Progressive, aka Bull Moose, ticket.</item>
        <item>Igor Stravinsky      #(1862-1971)  #Too many pieces of music finish too long after the end.#A Russian composer widely considered one of the most important and influential composers of the 20th century.  Stravinsky\'s compositional career was notable for its stylistic diversity. Most noted for his ballets The Firebird (1910), Petrushka (1911) and The Rite of Spring (1913). </item>
        <item>Ingrid Bergman       #(1915-1982)  #Happiness is good health and a bad memory.#A Swedish actress who starred in a variety of European and American films and winner of three Academy Awards. Ranked as the fourth greatest female star of American cinema of all time by the American Film Institute. Best remembered for her role as Ilsa Lund in Casablanca (1942), a World War II drama co-starring Humphrey Bogart.</item>
        <item>Jay Leno             #(b. 1050)   #If God wanted us to vote, he would have given us candidates.#An American comedian (and actor, voice actor, writer, producer and television host). Host of NBC\'s The Tonight Show with Jay Leno from 1992 to 2009.</item>
        <item>Jimi Hendrix         #(1942-1970)  #Excuse me while I kiss the sky.#An American musician (and singer and songwriter). Despite a relatively brief mainstream career spanning four years, he is widely regarded as one of the most influential electric guitarists in the history of popular music, and one of the most celebrated musicians of the 20th century.</item>
        <item>John Belushi         #(1949-1982)  #Christ, seven years of college, down the drain.#An American comedian (and actor and musician). He is best known as one of the original cast members of the hit NBC sketch comedy show Saturday Night Live.  He was known for his brash, energetic comedy style and raunchy humor.</item>
        <item>John F. Kennedy       #(1917-1963)  #Mankind must put an end to war before war puts an end to mankind.#An American president commonly known as \"Jack\" or by his initials JFK. Kennedy was the 35th President of the United States, serving from January 1961 until he was assassinated in November 1963.</item>
        <item>John Lennon          #(1940-1980)#Life is what happens while you are busy making other plans.#An English musician (and singer and songwriter) who rose to worldwide fame as a founding member of the Beatles. With Paul McCartney, he formed one of the most celebrated songwriting partnerships of the 20th century.</item>
        <item>John Wanamaker       #(1838-1922)  #Half the money I spend on advertising is wasted.  The trouble is I don\'t know which half.#An American merchant (and religious leader and civic and political figure), considered by some to be the father of modern advertising and a pioneer in marketing.</item>
        <item>Julian Assange       #(b. 1971)   #These big-package releases. There should be a cute name for them.#An Australian publisher and journalist. He is known as the editor-in-chief and founder of WikiLeaks, which publishes submissions of secret information, news leaks and classified media from anonymous news sources and whistleblowers.</item>
        <item>Justin Bieber        #(b. 1994)  #A hard as I\'ve tried, I don\'t know how not to be adorable.#A Canadian  musician (and actor, and singer-songwriter). With a global fan base, termed as "Beliebers", and over 40 million followers on Twitter, he was named by Forbes magazine in 2012 as the third-most powerful celebrity in the world.</item>
        <item>Lance Armstrong      #(b. 1971)  #The simple truth is that we outwork everyone.#An American cyclist who won the Tour de France a record seven consecutive times between 1999 and 2005. Due to doping offences, the U. S. Anti Doping Agency (USADA) in 2012 disqualified Armstrong from those races and banned him from competitive cycling for life.</item>
        <item>Lenny Bruce          #(1925-1966)  #Communism is like one big phone company.#An American comedian (and social critic and satirist). He was renowned for his open, free-style and critical form of comedy which integrated politics, religion, sex, and vulgarity. His private life was marked by substance abuse and promiscuity as well as efforts to prevent his wife from working as a stripper.</item>
        <item>Lily Tomlin          #(b. 1939)  #The trouble with the rat race is that even if you win, you\'re still a rat.#An American actress (and comedian, writer, and producer). Tomlin has been a major force in American comedy since the late 1960s when she began a career as a stand-up comedian and became a featured performer on television\'s Laugh-in.</item>
        <item>Lord Kelvin          #(1824-1907)  #When you cannot measure, your knowledge is of a meagre and unsatisfactory kind.#An Irish-British physicist and engineer.  Lord Kelvin is widely known for determining the correct value of absolute zero as approximately -273.15 Celsius.</item>
        <item>Mae West             #(1893-1980)  #When choosing between two evils, I always try the one I\'ve never tried before.#An American actress (and singer, playwright, screenwriter, and sex symbol) whose entertainment career spanned seven decades.</item>
        <item>Mahatma Ghandi       #(1869-1948)  #I believe in equality for everyone, except reporters and photographers.#The preeminent leader of Indian nationalism in British-ruled India. Employing nonviolent civil disobedience, Gandhi led India to independence and inspired movements for civil rights and freedom across the world.</item>
        <item>Margaret Thatcher    #(1925-2013)  #When you want someting said, ask a man. When you want something done, ask a woman.#A British politiciaon and Prime Minister from 1979 to 1990. She implemented policies that came to be known as Thatcherism.</item>
        <item>Marilyn Monroe       #(1926-1962)  #Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world.#An American actress (and model and singer), who became a major sex symbol, starring in a number of commercially successful motion pictures during the 1950s and early 1960s.</item>
        <item>Mark Twain           #(1835-1910)  #I didn’t have time to write a short letter, so I wrote a long one instead.#An American author and humorist, whose real name was Samuel Clemens. He wrote The Adventures of Tom Sawyer and its sequel, Adventures of Huckleberry Finn, the latter often called \"the Great American Novel\".</item>
        <item>Marshall McLuhan     #(1911-1980)  #The medium is the message.#A Canadian philosopher of communication theory and a public intellectual. His work is viewed as one of the cornerstones of the study of media theory, as well as having practical applications in the advertising and television industries.</item>
        <item>Martin Luther King, Jr.#(1929-1968) #In the End, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends.#An American pastor (and activist, humanitarian, and leader) in the African-American Civil Rights Movement. He is best known for his role in the advancement of civil rights using nonviolent civil disobedience based on his Christian beliefs.</item>
        <item>Mel Brooks            #(b. 1926)  #Tradegy is when I cut my finger.  Comedy is when you walk into an open sewer and die.#A film director best known as a creator of broad film farces and comic parodies. His most well known films include The Producers, Blazing Saddles, Young Frankenstein, Silent Movie, High Anxiety, and History of the World Part I.</item>
        <item>Miles Davis          #(1926-1991)  #A legend is an old man with a cane known for what he used to do.  I\'m stilling doing it.#A jazz musician (and trumpeter, bandleader, and composer). Widely considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, Miles Davis was, with his musical groups, at the forefront of several major developments in jazz music, including bebop, cool jazz, hard bop, modal jazz, and jazz fusion.</item>
        <item>Muhammed Ali         #(b. 1942)  #I am the greatest.  I said that even before I knew I was.#An American boxer generally considered among the greatest heavyweights in the sport\'s history. A controversial and polarizing figure, Ali is widely regarded for not only his skills in the ring but also the values he exemplified outside of it: religious freedom and racial justice.</item>
        <item>Napoleon Bonaparte   #(1769-1821)  #Glory is fleeting, but obscurity is forever.#A military leader and politician in France who rose to prominence during the latter stages of the French Revolution and its associated wars in Europe.</item>
        <item>Oprah Winfrey         #(b. 1954)  #I still have my feet on the ground.  I just wear better shoes.#A media proprietor (and talk show host, actress, producer, and philanthropist). Winfrey is best known for her multi-award-winning talk show The Oprah Winfrey Show which was the highest-rated program of its kind in history and was nationally syndicated from 1986 to 2011.</item>
        <item>Oscar Wilde          #(1854-1900)  #Always forgive your enemies. Nothing annoys them so much.#An Irish writer and poet. He is remembered for his epigrams, his only novel (The Picture of Dorian Gray), his plays, and the circumstances of his imprisonment and early death.</item>
        <item>P. T. Barnum         #(1810-1891)  #There\'s a sucker born every minute.#An American showman (and businessman, prankster, and entertainer) remembered for promoting celebrated hoaxes and for founding the circus that became the Ringling Bros. and Barnum &amp; Bailey Circus.</item>
        <item>Pablo Picasso        #(1881-1973)  #Give me a museum, and I\'ll fill it.#A Spanish painter and sculptor who spent most of his adult life in France. As one of the greatest artists of the 20th century, he is best known for co-founding the Cubist movement.</item>
        <item>Paris Hilton         #(b. 1981)  #The way I see it, you should live everyday like it\'s your birthday.#An American socialite (and actress and entertainer) and the great-granddaughter of Conrad Hilton, the founder of Hilton Hotels.  Her hard-partying lifestyle and  short-lived relationships with Leonardo DiCaprio and Oscar De La Hoya has made her a fixture in entertainment news. </item>
        <item>Pete Seeger          #(1919-2014)  #If I had a hammer, I\'d hammer in the morning.#A folk singer who had a string of hit records during the 1950s as a member of The Weavers. Seeger was blacklisted during the McCarthy Era and re-emerged on the public scene as a prominent singer of protest music in support of international disarmament, civil rights, counterculture, and environmental causes.</item>
        <item>Phyllis Diller       #(1917-2012)  #Housework can\'t kill you. But why take the chance?#An American comedian (and actress and voice artist) best known for her eccentric stage persona and her wild hair and clothes. Diller\'s voice acting roles included the Queen in A Bug\'s Life.</item>
        <item>P. E. Trudeau        #(1919-2000)  #Fuddle duddle.  #Canadian Prime Minister from April 20, 1968 to June 4, 1979, and again from March 3, 1980 to June 30, 1984.  Admirers praise the force of Trudeau\'s intellect[2] and salute his political acumen in preserving national unity.</item>
        <item>Plato                #(428-324 BC)  #At the touch of love everyone becomes a poet.#A Greek philosopher in the Classical age. He was also a mathematician, student of Socrates, writer of philosophical dialogues, and founder of the Academy in Athens, the first institution of higher learning in the Western world.</item>
        <item>Ralph Waldo Emerson  #(1803-1882)   #Build a better mousetrap and the world will beat a path to you door.#An American essayist (and lecturer and poet) who led the Transcendentalist movement of the mid-19th century. He disseminated his thoughts through dozens of published essays and more than 1,500 public lectures across the United States.</item>
        <item>Richard Dawkins      #(b. 1941)    #We are all atheists about most of the Gods humanity has ever believed in.  Some of us just go one God further.#An English biologist and author. He is an atheist, a subject on which he writes books and makes regular television and radio appearances.  His 206 book The God Delusion has sold more than two million copies.</item>
        <item>Richard Feynman      #(1918-1988)  #The philosophy of science is about as useful to scientists as ornithology is to birds.#An American physicist known for his work in the path integral formulation of quantum mechanics, the theory of quantum electrodynamics, and the physics of the superfluidity of supercooled liquid helium, as well as in particle physics (he proposed the parton model).</item>
        <item>Richard Nixon        #(1913-1994)  #When the President does it, that means it\'s not illegal.#An American President serving from 1969 to 1974, when he became the only president to resign the office.</item>
        <item>Rodney Dangerfield   #(1921-2004)  #My wife and I were happy for twenty years. Then we met!#An American comedian and actor, known for the catchphrase "I don't get no respect!" and his monologues on that theme. Remembered for his 1980s film roles in Easy Money, Caddyshack, and Back to School.</item>
        <item>Salvador Dali        #(1904-1989)  #The only difference between me and a madman is that I\'m not mad.#A surrealist painter born in Figueres, in the Catalonia region of Spain.  Dalí was a skilled draftsman, best known for the striking and bizarre images in his surrealist work. His painterly skills are often attributed to the influence of Renaissance masters.</item>
        <item>Samuel Johnson       #(1709-1784)  #Patriotism is the last refuge of the scoundrel.#An English writer who made lasting contributions to English literature as a poet, essayist, moralist, literary critic, biographer, editor and lexicographer. Often referred to as Dr. Johnson</item>
        <item>Sarah Palin          #(b. 1964)   #But obviously, we\'ve got to stand with our North Korean allies.#An American politician who served as Governor of Alaska from 2006 to 2009. As the Republican Party nominee for Vice President in the 2008, she was the first Alaskan on the national ticket of a major party and first Republican woman nominated for the vice presidency. Known for her sparse intellect and public speaking gaffs.</item>
        <item>Seneca               #(4 BC - 65 AD)#While we are posponing, life speeds by.#A Roman philosopher (and statesman, dramatist, and in one work humorist) of the Silver Age of Latin literature. He was tutor and later advisor to emperor Nero. While he was forced to commit suicide for alleged complicity in the Pisonian conspiracy to assassinate Nero, he may have been innocent.</item>
        <item>Stephen Harper        #(b. 1959)    #Kyoto is essentially a socialist scheme to suck money out of wealth-producing nations.#Canadian Prime Minister and leader of the Conservative Party. Harper became prime minister in 2006, forming a minority government.  In the 2011 election, Haper\'s Conservative Party won with a majority, winning 166 of 308 seats.</item>
        <item>Steve Martin          #(b. 1945)    #A day without sunshine is like, you know, night.#An American comedian (and actor, musician, author, screenwriter and film producer). Martin came to public notice as a writer for the Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour, and later became a frequent guest on The Tonight Show.</item>
        <item>Thomas Edison        #(1847-1931)  #I have not failed. I have just found 10,000 ways that don\'t work.#An American inventor and businessman. He developed many devices that greatly influenced life around the world, including the phonograph, the motion picture camera, and a long-lasting, practical electric light bulb.</item>
        <item>Thomas Jefferson     #(1743-1826)  #I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have.#A Founding Father of the United States and principal author of the Declaration of Independence (1776) and the third President of the United States (1801–1809). He was a spokesman for democracy and human rights.</item>
        <item>Tom Waits            #(b. 1949)  #I\'d rather have a bottle in front of me than a frontal lobotomy.#An American singer-songwriter (and composer, and actor). Waits has a distinctive voice, described by critic Daniel Durchholz as sounding \"like it was soaked in a vat of bourbon, left hanging in the smokehouse for a few months, and then taken outside and run over with a car.\"</item>
        <item>Virginia Woolf       #(1882-1941)  #For most of history, Anonymous was a woman.#An English writer and one of the foremost modernists of the twentieth century. During the interwar period, Woolf was a significant figure in London literary society and a central figure in the influential Bloomsbury Group of intellectuals.</item>
        <item>Voltaire             #(1694-1778)  #God is a comedian playing to an audience too afraid to laugh.#A French writer in the Enlightenment, historian and philosopher famous for his wit, his attacks on the established Catholic Church, and his advocacy of freedom of religion, freedom of expression, and separation of church and state.</item>
        <item>Walter Cronkite      #(1916-2009)  #The perils of duck hunting are great - expecially for the duck.#An American journalist in broadcast, best known as anchorman for the CBS Evening News for 19 years (1962–81). During the heyday of CBS News in the 1960s and 1970s, he was often cited as \"the most trusted man in America\" after being so named in an opinion poll.</item>
        <item>Warren Buffet        #(b. 1930)  #In the business world, the rearview mirror is always clearer than the windshield.#An business magnate (and investor, and philanthropist). He is widely considered the most successful investor of the 20th century. Buffett is the chairman, CEO and largest shareholder of Berkshire Hathaway and consistently ranked among the world\'s wealthiest people.</item>
        <item>Wayne Gretzky        #(b. 1961)  #You miss 100 percent of the shots you never take.#A hockey player who played 20 seasons in the NHL.  Nicknamed "The Great One", he has been called "the greatest hockey player ever" by many sportswriters, players, and the NHL itself. He is the only player to total over 200 points in a season – a feat he accomplished four times. </item>
        <item>Will Durant          #(1885-1981)  #Education is a progressive discovery of your own ignorance.#A American writer (and historian, and philosopher). He is best known for The Story of Civilization, 11 volumes written in collaboration with his wife Ariel Durant and published between 1935 and 1975.</item>
        <item>Winston Churchill    #(1874-1965)  #History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it.#A British politician who was the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom from 1940 to 1945 and again from 1951 to 1955. Widely regarded as one of the greatest wartime leaders of the 20th century.</item>
        <item>Woody Allen          #(b. 1935)   #Not only is there no God, but try finding a plumber on Sunday.#An American screenwriter (and director, actor, comedian, author, playwright, and musician) whose career spans more than 50 years. Allen has been nominated twenty-four times and won four Academy Awards: three for Best Original Screenplay and one for Best Director (Annie Hall, 1978).</item>
        <item>Yogi Berra           #(born 1925)  #The towels in that hotel room were so fluffy I could barely get my suitcase shut.#An baseball player (catcher and outfielder) and manager in Major League Baseball. He played almost his entire 19-year baseball career (1946–1965) for the New York Yankees.  Berra, who quit school after the eighth grade, was also known for his mangled quotes, such as \"It ain\'t over \'til it\'s over\".</item>
        <item>Yoko Ono             #(born 1933)  #Healing yourself is connected with healing others.#A Japanese artist and peace activist, known for her work in avant-garde art, music and filmmaking and for her 1969–1980 marriage to John Lennon.</item>
        <item>Zsa Zsa Gabor        #(born 1917)  #I call everyone \"Darling\" because I can\'t remember their names.#A Hungarian-born socialite and actress who acted in supporting roles in movies, on Broadway, and occasionally on television. She is known for having nine husbands, including hotel magnate Conrad Hilton.</item>
    </array>

</resources>