<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Demo_CardAnimation</string>
    <string name="description_image_1">Image 1</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Top News Stories of 2015</string>

    <string-array name="card_title">
        <item>#1 - Humboldt Broncos</item>
        <item>#2 - Economic Challenges</item>
        <item>#3 - Trudeau\'s Trade</item>
        <item>#4 - Legalization of Cannibis</item>
        <item>#5 - Trump\'s America</item>
        <item>#6 - Thai Cave Rescue</item>
        <item>#7 - Natural Disasters</item>
        <item>#8 - Human Suffering</item>
        <item>#9 - Toronto Homicides</item>
        <item>#10 - Royal Wedding</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="card_text">
        <!-- Summary text for top news stories -->
        <item>The bus crash on April 6 that left 16 people dead and 13 injured shocked the northern Saskatchewan city of
            Humboldt and reverberated throughout Canada and the hockey world. Among the dead were 10 players ranging in
            ages 16 to 21, and six team personnel.

            On Jan. 1, CTV Winnipeg bureau chief Jill Macyshon recaps our number one story of 2018 – of a town with a
            population of 6,000 rocked by the tragedy but united in support of their lost loved ones, with donors
            worldwide raising $15.2 million for victims’ families.
        </item>
        <item>Canada’s economy continues to grow and unemployment has fallen to its lowest level in 40 years, but after
            GM’s bombshell of an announcement to close its Oshawa plant and a downturn in the oil sector, the Liberal
            government is under great pressure to turn things around as it heads into an election year in 2019. CTV
            senior political correspondent Glen McGregor recaps the biggest news this year in Canada’s economy, on Dec.
            31.
        </item>
        <item>On Dec. 30, CTV Ottawa bureau chief Joyce Napier recaps a challenging year in trade for the Liberal
            government. From uncertainty over the Trans Mountain Expansion Project to a revamped NAFTA deal, signed
            after an acrimonious trade war with the U.S., it’s been a steep learning curve for a government looking for
            new trading partners on the international scene, realizing it needs to end total reliance on the U.S.
        </item>
        <item>CTV Montreal bureau chief Genevieve Beauchemin looks back on the year Canada’s marijuana laws became the
            focus of the world. Statistics Canada says Canadians bought $43-million worth of pot in the first two weeks
            after legalization went into effect on Oct. 17. But it’s clear that two months into legalization, the new
            pot regime is still working out kinks in the supply chain and the enforcement of new rules.
        </item>
        <item>On Dec. 28, CTV Washington bureau chief Joy Malbon recaps year two of U.S. President Donald Trump’s
            tumultuous term. From his presidential meeting with North Korean dictator Kim Jong Un, to hush money paid to
            porn star Stormy Daniels, to the continuing Russia investigation and the firings and resignations in his
            administration, it’s been quite the year for the 45th president, who faces a 2019 that could bring endless
            House investigations into his finances, Russian interference and ethics.
        </item>
        <item>The daring rescue of 12 children who were part of a Thai soccer team and their coach, caught deep inside
            the flooded Mae Sai cave complex in Chiang Rai, was number six in our top 10 stories of 2018. CTV’s Peter
            Akman on Dec. 27 recounts the drama that riveted the world and the stunning moment when British divers found
            the missing team.
        </item>
        <item>Few places in the world escaped natural disasters in 2018, from tornadoes that ripped through the Ottawa
            area in September to deadly hurricanes, cyclones, earthquakes and massive wildfires worldwide. CTV Atlantic
            bureau chief Todd Battis on Dec. 26 recounts the destruction that nature wreaked on Earth, and the fear that
            consequences of climate change could lead to even more calamitous events in the future.
        </item>
        <item>On Dec. 25, London bureau chief Paul Workman looks at the terrible cost of war and the millions of
            civilians it has left displaced and desperate this past year. From the plight of the Rohingya Muslims of
            Myanmar to the humanitarian crises unfolding in Yemen and Syria, thanks to conflicts that have dragged on
            for years. It has been a year of human suffering in many parts of the world.
        </item>
        <item>This has been an especially deadly year in Toronto, with the city notching more than 90 homicides so far
            amidst a spate of brazen shootings and calls for a handgun ban. The numbers eclipse the previous record of
            89 total homicides in 1991 and 80 in 2005, which was dubbed the “summer of the gun.”

            On Dec. 24, CTV Toronto bureau correspondent John Vennavally-Rao looks back at a year in which violent
            incidents—including the van attack and mass shooting on the Danforth—shocked and outraged the city.
        </item>
        <item>CTV London bureau correspondent Daniele Hamamdjian kicks off the top 10 countdown on Dec. 23, with a look
            back at Prince Harry and Meghan Markle’s extraordinary wedding. Hamamdjian reflects on the spectacle that
            attracted millions of viewers, the star-studded ceremony and the drama surrounding the former actress’s
            family.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Background colors for summary text -->
    <array name="card_background_color">
        <item>#2c355d</item>
        <item>#2f4d51</item>
        <item>#4c3327</item>
        <item>#70685b</item>
        <item>#b60a0a</item>
        <item>#777777</item>
        <item>#7777ff</item>
        <item>#59705a</item>
        <item>#d23c2d</item>
        <item>#6aaffd</item>
    </array>

</resources>